that
hello friends welcome all of you
once again to Job in Computer Gyan YouTube
channel the topic is
how to upload the husk of Paytm Payment Bank and do
group insurance of the customer,
I will tell you guys step by step in this video by
adopting it,
so if you guys are a customer to get group insurance,
then it is necessary to be at least 65 years old, the
customer should have the
photo editing setting of Paytm Payment Bank turned
on, whatever it is, if you guys come
to my tablet computer YouTube channel for the first
time then subscribe to my channel
and give me time and turn on the belt to
see my upcoming videos first, so let's
start with Paytm
Group Insurance Ad Lambert how do you guys have to
adopt it, first of all you have to open Paytm's
20 years,
after opening the PCL, you guys will see such interface in front of you,
Kolkata's Voices, Savings
Account, Fixed Deposit,
Atul Cassette means bank statement, cash
payment, Blessings Benefit Transfer and
that the old one has the option of group insurance in it,
now the latest version app lock
first  You have to download it which is the
latest version of point 652 right now, so my old one which
was 41518, I will
install it in the back of the old one and
this one which is point 65,
I will start it from the BC Agent app right now, I had
already downloaded it, so after
installing it in front of you, I will tell you whether
you get the option of group insurance in 46.5
or not, so
for this you have to
click on the writing in V shape in BC apps,
later the install option will come in front of you,
then click on install,
click on Store, the
installation process will come in front of you for some time,
then you will have to wait for a while,
after this you have the option of open in front of you, you
can see what is happening to me,
so I will click on open right now,
click on open and along with that, my app which has
come to you safely is Paytm Payment Bank,
first you have to
select the language, risk balance, now you have to do
pension and love.  After that, by
typing in your mobile number registered with Paytm Payment Bank BC Agent and
whatever your user ID or passport is, now after
entering the parameters and clicking on send,
after clicking on add, your OTP will come on your latest mobile number
which you had given at the time of doing the raw operation,
you will have to enter the OTP and
click on verify,
after clicking on the website, your
login will open in front of you through the app,
so I have entered voted and now I will
click on belt free,
after clicking on verify, your affection will go
well, Paytm Payment Bank BC app,
so you people will have to wait a bit, then you people
can see what is Paytm Payment Bank Basic
School, then you people have to click below, you can
see the
option of group inches,
on group inches you have to delete the inter cast
mobile number customer number, later
you people have to click on famous,
after clicking on famous you
people have to click on health insurance,
click on  Later
such an interface will come in front of you people, so you
people can see it, secondly, in
this third AC waiting room of ICICI Lombard Hospital, Delhi, you will get
telecast till the desk, friends benefit Pandey,
you people will get office benefit Pandey, Pandey
corn flour WhatsApp, people will have to
stay in the medical tally hospital, you will not
get this, there you will get
discharge social love for anxiety
and from request slap distance
from and you want next 9 from
whichever you want to take on account, Hospitalization
Anywhere in India Blue Police and
click on buy,
P rule building of GST rate in person
select Pune, you are sick, you will get four by holding
153 84384 flap clock, you will
get 500 to 1000 in the party, after this
you people will get Pandey 100 on the network,
now on desktop you will get
100 for 450, after this you will get
Pandey 208 on the side, all these people can
select any one minimum and first to
my  You have to click on it and
bring it from 150 so you can select any one pin up from them
after that
you have to click on the possible above
after clicking on the animals I have to fill the
interpersonal test which is taken by mixing digestive latest
in it I have to
become a mother dealer full name of nominee of
any other person of the house you
can give it in the row like your father Madhur
spouse Dr Shiv Base here I am giving my wife's name in rupees so from here
you can fill any
name
[music] of the
spice after this
we can fill the gender of the person then we just
email if not mail then I will
bring it from morning after this I will fill the date of birth of you
people from the filled Gandu ko mirchi ek karkege document me kuch dhal ho to aap lokmat bhari usko kabhi aap log ne dekh karein ka sakte hai so you can see the name of any
person of the house if you have filled the no majors
correctly or by
filling the plot top in Ramesh test you have to
click on famous after clicking on it
you will get your paytm list
mobile number plus six  A 1000 megapixel OTP will be sent
for verification, after that
you have to verify the account by entering the option
which has been
filled in your documents, so you
must enter the details on the inch, my name,
date of birth, details have been collected from the police,
it means you should check my details
properly, after that you will have to
click on the location, so I am
looking at my account that is abroad properly,
so you should check your current policy
properly, after that
you will click on post,
after clicking on WhatsApp, verify customer,
you have to do Aadhaar notification of Aadhaar and
education, later
₹1 will be deducted from the customer's Paytm Payment Bank savings account
and whatever payment of Rs 150 to the police is made, then
you can see the
insurance processing from the police, so you have to
wait a bit till the payment is made,
after the payment is made, the policy details will come up in front of you, the
police
number will come up, then the
approved policy number will be sent to your Paytm Payment Bank mobile number  If you
go then you
can get insurance through Paytm Payment Bank. If
you liked this video then
please like, share and subscribe. Thank you
for watching.
[Music]